Guide to the Cornell University and Ithaca views and guidebooks, 1873-1982.
Cornell University and Ithaca views and guidebooks,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University and Ithaca views and guidebooks, 1873-1982.
4059
26 volumes.
4 items.
Printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Guidebooks and books of views of Cornell University and Ithaca, N.Y.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Guidebooks and books of views of Cornell University and Ithaca, N.Y.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Perkins, Frank C. (Frank Clinton), 1867-; Thurber, Charles H. (Charles Herbert), 1864-1938.; Sheldon, Seth L.; Cornell University; Cornell University; Cornell University -- History.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University -- Athletics.; Sibley College of Mechanical Engineering and Mechanic Arts; New York State College of Agriculture; Cornell University; New York State College of Agriculture; Sibley College of Mechanical Engineering and Mechanic Arts; Business Men's Association of Ithaca (N.Y.).; Cornell University.; Albertype Co.; Cornell Co-Operative Society.; Student Supply Store
Subjects:
Rowing.; Galvanometer.; Athletics; Galvanometer; Rowing; Students; Universities and colleges -- Faculty
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.); Ithaca (N.Y.); New York (State) -- Ithaca
Form and Genre Terms:
Travel guidebooks.; Photogravures.; Postcards,; Guidebooks; History; Pictorial works
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Campus Guide, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Fold-out Map
- Campus Guide, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Guide to Cornell University, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Map, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ithaca, NY in Tompkins County: Heart of the Finger Lakes Region, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Students' Handbook of the Region about Ithaca, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- This is Cornell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Brochure Advertisement
- Campus Walks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Brochure Advertisement- Three copies, two annotated
- The Cornell Plantations Vol XXVI, No 3, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Publication with Articles
- The Proposed Residential Halls: Cornell University- Ithaca, New York, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Brochure, property of Thomas W. Mackesey
- The Statue of Ezra Cornell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Brochure
- The Cornell Plantations: The Suspension Bridge, 1982-05-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Mailing
- Some Views of the State College of Agriculture Cornell University Ithaca, New York, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Photo- "Main Lab", Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Scientific American Photocopies, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Saul Ash Company Catalog, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Unbound Book Pages on Cornell University, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cornell and Ithaca, 1919-06 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Photobook- 2 copies
- Photo Album- Ithaca and Cornell, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Photo Album- Ithaca and Cornell, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Photo Album- Cornell University and Ithaca, 1907; Publisher- Taylor and Carpenter (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Photo Album- Cornell University and Ithaca, 1906; Publisher- Taylor and Carpenter (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Photo Album- Cornell University and Ithaca, Undated; Publisher- Taylor and Carpenter (Box 1, Folder 10)
- An Album- Photos of students and faculty, 1890-1910; Publisher- University Publishing Society (Box 1)
- Manila Envelope of Photos of Cornell Buildings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Scenic Colored Miniatures of Ithaca, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University: A Book of Pictures, Undated; Publisher- Cornell University; Property of RP. Atherton (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University Views, Undated; Publisher- Andrus and Church (Box 1, Folder 12)
  The University Records, Series 1 No. 3 Part 2
- Views of Ithaca and Cornell University (3rd Edition), Undated; Publisher- Andrus and Church (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University: Her General and Technical Courses, 1891; Publisher- Frank C. Perkins; Gift of Class of 1923 (Box 1)
- Official Publications of Cornell University: The Campus of Cornell University: A Book of Views, 1911-04-01; Publisher- Cornell University (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University: Photo-Gravures, 1897; Publisher- Taylor and Preswick (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Photographic Gems: Being a Collection og Views of Cornell University by Seth L. Sheldon, 1898; Brittle Book (Box 1)
- The University Guide, Containing an Account of the Buildings, Museums, and Collections of Cornell University, 1875; Publisher- Finch and Apgar (Box 1)
- Cornell University: Photo-Gravures, 1895; Publisher- Dudley F. Finch (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Views of Ithaca and Cornell University (4th Edition), Undated; Publisher- Andrus and Church (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A Guide Book to Cornell University and Ithaca, 1904; Publisher- Silver, Burdett and Company (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Picturesque Ithaca: Photo-Gravures, 1896; Publisher- Taylor and Preswick (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell and Ithaca Views: Photos, Undated; Publisher- Andrus and Church (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell and Ithaca Views: Photos, Undated; Publisher- Andrus and Church (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ithaca and Cornell University: Photo-Gravures, Undated; Publisher- The Corner Bookstores (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ithaca and Cornell: In the Heart of the Finger Lakes- Photo Album, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Some Suggestions About Ithaca and its Business Resources, Undated; Publisher- The Business Men's Association of Ithaca (Box 1, Folder 14)
- In and Out of Ithaca, 1887; Publisher- Andrus and Church; Brochure (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Views of Ithaca: Photo Album, 1906; Publisher- RC Osborn and Company (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Familiar Views at Cornell University: Photo Album, 1916; Publisher- Cornell Cooperative Society (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Troy Daily Times Clippings, including "A Romantic Story. Founding of Cornell University", 1893-1898 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Scientific American Clippings, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Loose Book Pages: Cornell University, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Photo: Sage Chapel, North Transept, West Entry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1876-08-05 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Scientific American Front Page, 1885-09-19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Scientific American Front Page, 1890-10-11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Harper's Weekly Clippings, 1875-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Cornell University: Photo-Gravures, 1895; Publisher- Dudley F. Finch (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cornell University: Photo-Gravures, Undated; Publisher- Student Supply Store Inc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Loose Book Pages: Photos, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- The Cornell Book: Photo Album, 1914; Publisher- Student Supply Store Inc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cornell, Undated (Box 3)
  Contains 30 photograveurs, plus one additional one of Taughannock Falls. Cover has letters HBY or MBY printed under the word Cornell.
- Glimpses of Ithaca and Cornell: Book of Postcards, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cornell in Pictures, 1941-12-16 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Gift of Estate of Walter L. Todd Class 1909
- Framed photograph University and grounds, Circa 1870 (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Framed pages from Harper's Weekly showing campus, Circa 1875 (Mapcase-folder 1)
- East View of Ithaca, Tompkins County, NY, 1836 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  Reproduction